easyayurveda.com 2019-05-06

# Privacy Policy - Easy Ayurveda

At easyayurveda.com, we respect every individual’s right to privacy. Our relationship with you is our most valuable asset and is the very basis of our name and reputation.

We understand the importance you place on the privacy and security of information that personally identifies you or your account information.

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://easyayurveda.com (the “Site”).

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

– “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.  
– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.  
For this purpose, we use  
Google Analytics And  
Google DoubleClick For Publishers

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment informatio), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”  
We do not store your credit card information or ATM card, net banking or cash card information or any such payment informations.  
When you purchase goods or services from us, your payment information is secured in our payment services providers –  
paypal.com  
Ccavenue.com or  
payumoney.com

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:  
Communicate with you;  
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and  
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING  
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads  
GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous  
BING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads  
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.

WordPress tools used:

### Contact Form

 **Data Used:**  [Akismet](https://akismet.com/) is enabled on the site, the contact form submission data of IP address, user agent, name, email address, website, and message — is submitted to the [Akismet](https://akismet.com/) service (also owned by [Automattic](https://automattic.com/)) for the sole purpose of spam checking. The actual submission data is stored in the database of the site on which it was submitted and is emailed directly to the owner of the form (i.e. the site author who published the page on which the contact form resides). This email will include the submitter’s IP address, timestamp, name, email address, website, and message.

 **Data Synced ([?](https://jetpack.com/support/what-data-does-jetpack-sync/)):** Post and post meta data associated with a user’s contact form submission. [Akismet](https://akismet.com/) is enabled on the site, the IP address and user agent originally submitted with the comment are synced, as well, as they are stored in post meta.

DO NOT TRACK  
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

YOUR RIGHTS  
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

DATA RETENTION  
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

CHANGES  
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

CONTACT US  
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at hebbarjv@gmail.com or by mail using the details provided below:  
Flat no. 201, Datta Garden, 5th Cross, MG Road, Beside Lalitha Kala Arts, Mangaluru, KA, 575003, India.
